Guide to the Stereograph File [1855-1964] (Bulk 1860-1900) PR 65
© 2011 New-York Historical Society
  - New York--Niagara Falls--Rapids and river views, [ca. 1856-1908] (Box 48)
  - New York--Niagara Falls--Winter scenes, [ca. 1860-ca. 1910] (Box 49)
  - New York--North Elba, [ca. 186-- ca. 187-] (Box 49)
  - New York--Norton Hill, [ca. 187-] (Box 49)
  - New York--Nyack, [ca. 1860-1876] (Box 49)
  - New York--Olean, [ca. 1900] (Box 49)
  - New York--Ossining, [ca. 187--ca. 1880] (Box 49)
  - New York--Oswego, [ca. 186--ca. 187-] (Box 50)
  - New York--Otsego Lake, [ca. 1870] (Box 50)
  - New York--Ovid, [ca. 186-] (Box 50)
  - New York--Palensville, [ca. 187-] (Box 50)
  - New York--Palmer's Falls, [ca. 187-] (Box 50)
  - New York--Peekskill, [ca. 186--] (Box 50)
  - New York--Penn Yan, [ca. 1870] (Box 50)
  - New York--Plum Island, [ca. 1870] (Box 50)
  - New York--Port Jervis, [ca. 1870] (Box 50)
  - New York--Port Chester, [ca. 1870] (Box 50)
  - New York--Portage, [ca. 1858-ca. 1890] (Box 50)
  - New York--Poughkeepsie, [ca. 1870-ca. 1900] (Box 50)
  - New York--Ramapo, [186-] (Box 50)
  - New York--Restof, 1907 (Box 50)
  - New York--Richfield Springs, [ca. 1865-187-] (Box 50)
  - New York--Rifton, 1946 (Box 50)
  - New York--Rochester, [1859-ca. 1895] (Box 50)
  - New York--Rondout, [ca. 1875] (Box 50)
  - New York--Roseindale, [ca. 1870] (Box 50)
  - New York--Round Lake, [ca. 1865] (Box 50)
  - New York--Salamanca, 1908 (Box 50)
  - New York--Saranac Lake, [ca. 187--ca. 188-] (Box 50)
  - New York--Saratoga Springs--Amusements, [ca. 1865-ca. 1900] (Box 50)
  - New York--Saratoga Springs--Broadway, [ca. 187-] (Box 50)
  - New York--Saratoga Springs--Buildings, [ca. 1865-ca. 1880] (Box 50)
  - New York--Saratoga Springs--Hotels, [ca. 1860-ca. 1880] (Box 51)
  - New York--Saratoga Springs--Hotels -- Congress Hall and Park, [ca. 1865-ca. 1885] (Box 51)
  - New York--Saratoga Springs--Hotels -- Clarendon Hotel, [ca. 187-] (Box 51)
  - New York--Saratoga Springs--Hotels -- Grand Hotel, [187-] (Box 51)
  - New York--Saratoga Springs--Hotels -- Grand Union Hotel, [ca. 1865-ca. 1880] (Box 51)
  - New York--Saratoga Springs--Hotels -- United States Hotel, [ca. 1870-ca. 1885] (Box 51)
  - New York--Saratoga Springs--Lakes and scenery, [ca. 1865-ca. 1885] (Box 51)
  - New York--Saratoga Springs--People, [ca. 1865-ca.-ca. 1880] (Box 51)
  - New York--Saratoga Springs--Springs, [ca. 1860-ca. 1885] (Box 51)
  - New York--Scarsdale, 1862 (Box 52)
  - New York--Schenectady, [ca. 1880] (Box 52)
  - New York--Schroon Lake, [187-] (Box 52)
  - New York--Sharon Springs, [ca. 1860-187-] (Box 52)
  - New York--Silver Lake, [ca. 1884-1891] (Box 52)
  - New York--Skaneateles Lake, [ca. 188-] (Box 52)
  - New York--Springville, 1885 (Box 52)
  - New York--Starucca Creek, [ca. 1860-187-] (Box 52)
  - New York--Sterling Forest, 1962 (Box 52)
  - New York--Syracuse and vicinity, [ca. 1860-ca. 1900] (Box 52)
  - New York--Tarrytown, [ca. 1865-1959] (Box 52)
  - New York--Taughannock Falls, [ca. 187-] (Box 52)
  - New York--Thousand Islands, [187--188-] (Box 52)
  - New York--Ticonderoga, [187--188-] (Box 52)
  - New York--Trenton Falls, [ca. 1856-187-] (Box 52)
  - New York--Troy, [187--188-] (Box 52)
  - New York--Union Springs, [ca. 1870] (Box 52)
  - New York--Walton, [ca. 1865] (Box 52)
  - New York--Warsaw, [ca. 1870] (Box 52)
  - New York--Watervliet, [ca. 1870] (Box 52)
  - New York--Watkins Glen, [ca. 1860-1900] (Box 53)
  - New York--Weedsport, [ca. 1870] (Box 53)
  - New York--West Point, [ca. 1856-19] (Box 53)
  - New York--Whitehall, [ca. 186--187-] (Box 54)
  - New York--Yonkers, [ca. 1865-1959] (Box 54)
  - North Carolina, [ca. 187--1903] (Box 54)
  - North Dakota, [ca. 1873-ca. 1900] (Box 54)
  - Ohio, [ca. 187--ca. 1901] (Box 54)
  - Ohio--Cincinnati, [ca. 1865-ca. 1900] (Box 54)
  - Ohio--Cleveland, [ca. 187--1896] (Box 54)
  - Oklahoma, [ca. 187-] (Box 54)
  - Oregon, [ca. 1867-1902] (Box 54)
  - Pennsylvania, [ca. 1865-1903] (Box 54)
  - Pennsylvania--Pennsylvania Railroad, [ca. 1860-1903] (Box 54)
  - Pennsylvania--Canals, [ca. 187-] (Box 54)
  - Pennsylvania--Catawissa Creek, [ca. 1865-187-] (Box 54)
  - Pennsylvania--Delaware River, [ca. 1860-1883] (Box 55)
  - Pennsylvania--Johnstown Flood, 1889 (Box 55)
  - Pennsylvania--Lehigh Valley and Mauch Chunk, [ca. 1867-188-] (Box 55)
  - Pennsylvania--Oil region, [ca. 1860-1903] (Box 55)
  - Pennsylvania--Philadelphia, [187-] (Box 55)
  - Pennsylvania--Philadelphia--Bridges, [ca. 1870-ca. 1885] (Box 55)
  - Pennsylvania--Philadelphia--Carpenter's Hall, [187-] (Box 56)
  - Pennsylvania--Philadelphia--Centennial -- Grounds, 1876 (Box 56)
  - Pennsylvania--Philadelphia--Centennial -- Washington Carriage, 1876 (Box 56)
  - Pennsylvania--Philadelphia--Centennial -- Buildings, 1876 (Box 56)
  - Pennsylvania--Philadelphia--Centennial--Buildings, Agricultural, 1876 (Box 56)
  - Pennsylvania--Philadelphia--Centennial--Buildings, Art Gallery, 1876 (Box 56)
  - Pennsylvania--Philadelphia--Centennial--Buildings, Art displays, 1876 (Box 56)
  - Pennsylvania--Philadelphia--Centennial -- Buildings, Horticulture, 1876 (Box 56)
  - Pennsylvania--Philadelphia--Centennial -- Buildings, Machinery, 1876 (Box 56)
  - Pennsylvania--Philadelphia--Centennial -- Buildings, Main, 1876 (Box 57)
  - Pennsylvania--Philadelphia--Centennial -- Buildings, States, 1876 (Box 57)
  - Pennsylvania--Philadelphia--Centennial -- Buildings, United States, 1876 (Box 57)
  - Pennsylvania--Philadelphia--Centennial -- Buildings, Women's, 1876 (Box 57)
  - Pennsylvania--Philadelphia--Churches, [186--188-] (Box 57)
  - Pennsylvania--Philadelphia--Colleges and universities, [186--188-] (Box 57)
  - Pennsylvania--Philadelphia--Commercial buildings, [186--188-] (Box 57)
  - Pennsylvania--Philadelphia--Government buildings, [ca. 1870-188-] (Box 57)
  - Pennsylvania--Philadelphia--Hotels, [187-] (Box 57)
  - Pennsylvania--Philadelphia--Independence Hall, [186--1904] (Box 57)
  - Pennsylvania--Philadelphia--Newspaper buildings, [187-] (Box 57)
  - Pennsylvania--Philadelphia--Organizations, [ca. 187-] (Box 57)
  - Pennsylvania--Philadelphia--Fairmount Park, [ca. 1865-ca. 1900] (Box 58)
  - Pennsylvania--Philadelphia--Sanitary Fair, 1864 (Box 58)
  - Pennsylvania--Philadelphia--General, Street views, undated (Box 58)
  - Pennsylvania--Philadelphia--Wissahickon Creek, [ca. 1865-ca. 1880] (Box 58)
  - Pennsylvania--Pit Hole City Fire, 1869 (Box 58)
  - Pennsylvania--Tarentum, [ca. 1910] (Box 58)
  - Pennsylvania--Titusville, [186-] (Box 58)
  - Rhode Island, [ca. 1870-ca. 189-] (Box 58)
  - Rhode Island--Block Island, [ca. 188-] (Box 58)
  - Rhode Island--Narrangansett, [1867-ca. 1900] (Box 58)
  - Rhode Island--Newport, [ca. 1856-1901] (Box 58)
  - Rhode Island--Pawtucket, [1872- ca. 1880] (Box 58)
  - Rhode Island--Providence, [186--ca. 1880] (Box 58)
  - South Carolina, [ca. 1865-1902] (Box 58)
  - South Carolina--Aiken, [186--188-] (Box 59)
  - South Carolina--Beaufort, [186-] (Box 59)
  - South Carolina--Charleston, [ca. 1865-188-] (Box 59)
  - South Dakota, [187--ca. 1900] (Box 59)
  - South Dakota--Black Hills, [187--ca. 1900] (Box 59)
  - South Dakota--Fort Randall--Sioux prisoners of war, 1882 (Box 59)
  - Tennessee, [ca. 1870-1895] (Box 59)
  - Texas, [ca. 1865-1900] (Box 59)
  - Utah, [ca. 1865-] (Box 59)
  - Utah--Cottonwood Canyon area, [186--188-] (Box 59)
  - Utah--Echo Canyon area, [ca. 1866-188-] (Box 59)
  - Utah--Mormons, [ca. 1866-188-] (Box 60)
  - Utah--Ogden, [186--187-] (Box 60)
  - Utah--Salt Lake City and Great Salt Lake, [ca. 1865-1897] (Box 60)
  - Utah--Salt Lake City--Temple and Tabernacle, [ca. 1860-1901] (Box 60)
  - Utah--Union Pacific Railroad, [186-] (Box 60)
  - Utah--Weber Canyon, undated (Box 60)
  - Utah--Zion Canyon, [ca. 188-] (Box 61)
  - Vermont, [ca. 1865-ca. 188-] (Box 61)
  - Vermont--Bellows Falls, [ca. 1865-ca. 188-] (Box 61)
  - Vermont--St. Johnsbury, [1859-ca. 1885] (Box 61)
  - Vermont--Sheldon, [ca. 1870] (Box 61)
  - Vermont--Waterbury, [ca. 1870] (Box 61)
  - Virginia, [ca. 1860-1902] (Box 61)
  - Virginia--Arlington, [ca. 1865-1903] (Box 61)
  - Virginia--Mount Vernon, [ca. 1860-190] (Box 61)
  - Virginia--Richmond, [ca. 1865-ca. 188-] (Box 61)
  - Washington, [ca. 1872-1902] (Box 61)
  - West Virginia, undated (Box 61)
  - West Virginia--Harpers Ferry, [ca. 1859-ca. 1875] (Box 61)
  - Wisconsin, [ca. 1870-ca. 1905] (Box 62)
  - Wisconsin--Wisconsin Dells, [ca. 1870-ca. 1905] (Box 62)
  - Wyoming, [ca. 187-] (Box 62)
  - Wyoming--Union Pacific Railroad, [ca. 1866-187-] (Box 62)
  - Wyoming--Yellowstone, [ca. 1870-1904] (Box 62)
  - United States--Unidentified, [ca. 1860-ca. 188-] (Box 62)
  - United States--Glass, various photographers, [ca. 1856-1862] (Box 63)
  - United States--Glass, Babbitt, before 1860 (Box 63)
  - United States--Glass, Evans, before 1860 (Box 63)
  - United States--Glass, Langenheim, [ca. 1856] (Box 63)
  - United States--Tintypes, [ca. 187-] (Box 64)
  - Europe--Glass, [ca. 1855-ca. 1865] (Box 64)
  - Unidentified--Autochrome, [ca. 1910] (Box 64)
  - Foreign--World's views series, [ca. 190-] (Box 64)
  - Canada--British Columbia, [ca. 187--1903] (Box 64)
  - Canada--Lake Superior scenery, [187-] (Box 64)
  - Canada, Manitoba, [ca. 1900] (Box 64)
  - Canada, New Brunswick--Saint John, [187-] (Box 64)
  - Canada, Nova Scotia, [186--187-] (Box 64)
  - Canada, Ontario, [ca. 1860-1890] (Box 64)
  - Canada, Quc, [187--188-] (Box 64)
  - Canada, Quc--Quc, [ca. 186--ca. 1910] (Box 64)
  - Canada, Quc--Montr, [186--189-] (Box 64)
  - Honduras--Copan site, [ca. 188-] (Box 64)
  - Mexico, [1873-ca. 1900] (Box 64)
  - Panama, [ca. 1904] (Box 64)
  - Caribbean, [ca. 1880-1902] (Box 65)
  - Caribbean, Bermuda, [ca. 1870-ca. 1890] (Box 65)
  - Caribbean, Cuba, 1860-1901 (Box 65)
  - Europe, Austria, [ca. 1866-ca. 1910] (Box 65)
  - Europe, Belgium, [ca. 1865-1894] (Box 65)
  - Europe, Bulgaria, [ca. 1910] (Box 65)
  - Europe, Czech Republic, [ca. 1860] (Box 65)
  - Europe, Denmark, [ca. 1910] (Box 65)
  - Europe, England, [ca. 1856-1900] (Box 65)
  - Europe, England--London and vicinity, [ca. 1860-ca. 1905] (Box 66)
  - Europe, England--London and vicinity--British Museum, [ca. 187-] (Box 66)
  - Europe, England--London and vicinity--Crystal Palace, 1862 (Box 66)
  - Europe, France, [ca. 1857-ca. 189-] (Box 66)
  - Europe, France--Paris, [ca. 1860-ca. 1910] (Box 67)
  - Europe, France--Paris--Expositions, 1867-1900 (Box 67)
  - Europe, Germany, [ca. 1860-ca. 1910] (Box 67)
  - Europe, Greece, [ca. 186--1901] (Box 68)
  - Europe, Ireland, [ca. 1860-ca. 1910] (Box 68)
  - Europe, Italy, [ca. 1865-ca. 1900] (Box 68)
  - Europe, Italy--Rome, [ca. 1860-ca. 1910] (Box 68)
  - Europe, Luxembourg, [ca. 186-] (Box 69)
  - Europe, Malta, [ca. 187-] (Box 69)
  - Europe, Monaco, [ca. 187--ca. 1900] (Box 69)
  - Europe, Netherlands, [ca. 187--ca. 1900] (Box 69)
  - Europe, Norway, [1896-ca. 1910] (Box 69)
  - Europe, Poland, [ca. 1900] (Box 69)
  - Europe, Russia, [ca. 188--ca. 1920] (Box 69)
  - Europe, Scotland, [ca. 186--187-] (Box 69)
  - Europe, Spain, [ca. 188-] (Box 69)
  - Europe, Sweden, [1896-ca. 1910] (Box 69)
  - Europe, Switzerland, [ca. 1860-ca. 1910] (Box 69)
  - Europe, Wales, [ca. 186--187-] (Box 69)
  - Europe, unknown, [ca. 185--ca. 187-] (Box 69)
  - Africa, Egypt, [ca. 1858-ca. 1900] (Box 69)
  - Africa, South Africa, [ca. 188--1900] (Box 70)
  - Asia, China, [ca. 1860-ca. 1905] (Box 70)
  - Asia, Holy Land, [ca. 1860-ca. 1905] (Box 70)
  - Asia, India, 1899-1903 (Box 70)
  - Asia, Japan, [1896-ca. 1905] (Box 70)
  - Asia, Philippines, [ca. 1900] (Box 70)
  - Asia, Sri Lanka, 1903 (Box 70)
  - Asia, Turkey, [ca. 186-] (Box 70)
  - Subjects--African Americans, [ca. 186--ca. 1900] (Box 70)
  - Subjects--Agriculture, [ca. 1860-1901] (Box 70)
  - Subjects--Agriculture, Maple sugar, [ca. 1880-ca. 1910] (Box 70)
  - Subjects--Animals, undated (Box 71)
  - Subjects--Art, [ca. 1870-ca. 189-] (Box 71)
  - Subjects--Astronomy, [ca. 1859-1891] (Box 71)
  - Subjects--Automobiles, [ca. 1910] (Box 71)
  - Subjects--Botany, [ca. 1860-1901] (Box 71)
  - Subjects--Bridges, [ca. 187-] (Box 71)
  - Subjects--Circuses and shows, [ca. 189-] (Box 71)
  - Subjects--Circuses and shows--Buffalo Bill's Wild West Show, [188--ca. 1910] (Box 71)
  - Subjects--Civil War, [ca. 1863-ca. 189-] (Box 71)
  - Subjects--Civil War--African Americans, [1863-188-] (Box 71)
  - Subjects--Civil War--Camp Life, [ca. 1861-1865] (Box 71)
  - Subjects--Civil War--Dead, 1861-1865 (Box 71)
  - Subjects--Civil War--Hospitals, [ca. 1862-ca. 1865] (Box 71)
  - Subjects--Civil War--Navy, [ca. 1861-ca. 1865] (Box 72)
  - Subjects--Civil War--Portraits, Civilians, 1862-1886 (Box 72)
  - Subjects--Civil War--Portraits, Lincoln, before 1865 (Box 72)
  - Subjects--Civil War--Portraits, Officers, [ca. 1861-ca. 1865] (Box 72)
  - Subjects--Civil War--Portraits, Soldiers, [ca. 1861-caa. 1865] (Box 72)
  - Subjects--Civil War--Railroads, [ca. 1861-ca. 1865] (Box 72)
  - Subjects--Civil War--Alabama, [ca. 1864] (Box 72)
  - Subjects--Civil War--Washington, D.C., [ca. 1861-ca. 1865] (Box 72)
  - Subjects--Civil War--Florida, [ca. 1861-ca. 1865] (Box 72)
  - Subjects--Civil War--Georgia, [ca. 1862-ca. 1865] (Box 72)
  - Subjects--Civil War--Georgia, Atlanta, [ca. 1861-ca. 1865] (Box 72)
  - Subjects--Civil War--Maryland, 1861-1864 (Box 72)
  - Subjects--Civil War--Maryland, Antietam, 1862 (Box 73)
  - Subjects--Civil War--Mississippi, 1864 (Box 73)
  - Subjects--Civil War--New York, [ca. 1861-ca. 1865] (Box 73)
  - Subjects--Civil War--New York, Union Square Rally, 1861 (Box 73)
  - Subjects--Civil War--North Carolina, [ca. 1861-ca. 1865] (Box 73)
  - Subjects--Civil War--Pennsylvania, Gettysburg, 1863 (Box 73)
  - Subjects--Civil War--South Carolina, [ca. 1861-ca 1865] (Box 73)
  - Subjects--Civil War--South Carolina, Beaufort, [ca. 1861-ca. 1865] (Box 73)
  - Subjects--Civil War--South Carolina, Charleston, [ca. 1864-ca. 1865] (Box 73)
  - Subjects--Civil War--South Carolina, Fort Moultrie, [ca. 1861-1867] (Box 73)
  - Subjects--Civil War--South Carolina, Fort Sumter, [1861-ca. 1865] (Box 73)
  - Subjects--Civil War--Tennessee, [ca. 1861-ca. 1865] (Box 74)
  - Subjects--Civil War--Virginia, [ca. 1861-1865] (Box 74)
  - Subjects--Civil War--Virginia, Alexandria, [ca. 1861-ca. 1865] (Box 74)
  - Subjects--Civil War--Virginia, Appomattox, [ca. 1965] (Box 74)
  - Subjects--Civil War--Virginia, Bull Run, [ca. 1861-ca. 1865] (Box 74)
  - Subjects--Civil War--Virginia, Cedar Mountain, 1862 (Box 74)
  - Subjects--Civil War--Virginia, City Point, 1864-1865 (Box 74)
  - Subjects--Civil War--Virginia, Fair Oaks, 1862 (Box 74)
  - Subjects--Civil War--Virginia, Fortress Monroe, [ca. 1863] (Box 74)
  - Subjects--Civil War--Virginia, Fredericksburg, 1863 (Box 74)
  - Subjects--Civil War--Virginia, James River, [ca. 1862- 1865] (Box 75)
  - Subjects--Civil War--Virginia, North Anna River, 1863-1864 (Box 75)
  - Subjects--Civil War--Virginia, Petersburg, 1864-1865 (Box 75)
  - Subjects--Civil War--Virginia, Richmond, [ca. 1860-1865] (Box 75)
  - Subjects--Civil War--Virginia, Spotsylvania, 1864 (Box 75)
  - Subjects--Civil War--Virginia, Yorktown, [ca. 1862] (Box 75)
  - Subjects--Civil War--West Virginia, Harpers Ferry, [ca. 1865] (Box 75)
  - Subjects--Expositions and fairs, [ca. 1900] (Box 76)
  - Subjects--Expeditions--Fisk, 1866 (Box 76)
  - Subjects--Expeditions--Hayden, 1870-1875 (Box 76)
  - Subjects--Expeditions--Powell, 1871-1879 (Box 76)
  - Subjects--Expeditions--Selfridge (Darien), 1870 (Box 77)
  - Subjects--Expeditions--Wheeler, 1871-1874 (Box 77)
  - Subjects--Fires and fire equipment, [ca. 187-] (Box 77)
  - Subjects--Horse-drawn vehicles, [ca. 187--1890] (Box 77)
  - Subjects--Hotels, [ca. 1860-ca. 188-] (Box 77)
  - Subjects--Hunting and fishing, [ca. 1874-ca. 192-] (Box 77)
  - Subjects--Indians of North America, [186--ca. 1900] (Box 77)
  - Subjects--Lighthouses, [ca. 187-] (Box 78)
  - Subjects--Manufacturing, [ca. 186--ca. 187-] (Box 78)
  - Subjects--Medical, [ca. 187-] (Box 78)
  - Subjects--Mining, [ca. 187--1890] (Box 78)
  - Subjects--Occupations, [ca. 186--ca. 188-] (Box 78)
  - Subjects--Photographica--Manufacture and use, [ca. 186--1901] (Box 78)
  - Subjects--Photographica--Novelties, [ca. 186--1901] (Box 78)
  - Subjects--Photographica--Deterioration treatment samples, [ca. 187-] (Box 78)
  - Subjects--Portraits--A-C, 1858-1900 (Box 78)
  - Subjects--Portraits--D-J, [ca. 186--1901] (Box 78)
  - Subjects--Portraits--K-N, 1858-1900 (Box 78)
  - Subjects--Portraits--0-S, [186--ca. 1910] (Box 78)
  - Subjects--Portraits--T-Z, [186--1909] (Box 78)
  - Subjects--Portraits--Bagoe family, [ca. 1905-ca. 1915] (Box 79)
  - Subjects--Portraits--Lincoln assassination and funeral, 1865 (Box 79)
  - Subjects--Portraits--McKinley, William, 1896-1901 (Box 80)
  - Subjects--Portraits--Roosevelt, Theodore, [ca. 1890-ca. 1915] (Box 80)
  - Subjects--Portraits--Theatrical, [1858-ca. 188-] (Box 80)
  - Subjects--Portraits--Unidentified children, [ca. 187-] (Box 80)
  - Subjects--Portraits--Unidentified men, [ca. 1860-ca. 1890] (Box 80)
  - Subjects--Portraits--Unidentified women, [ca. 1865-ca. 1880] (Box 80)
  - Subjects--Portraits--Unidentified groups, [1859-ca. 1900] (Box 81)
  - Subjects--Railroads, [ca. 186--ca. 188-] (Box 81)
  - Subjects--Railroads--Pullman series, [ca. 1866] (Box 81)
  - Subjects--Religion, [ca. 1860-1901] (Box 81)
  - Subjects--Residences, [ca. 196--ca. 188-] (Box 81)
  - Subjects--Residences--Interiors, [ca. 186--ca. 188-] (Box 81)
  - Subjects--Schools and colleges, [ca. 186--188-] (Box 81)
  - Subjects--Sculpture, [ca. 186--ca. 187-] (Box 81)
  - Subjects--Ships, [ca. 1858-ca. 1910] (Box 81)
  - Subjects--Ships--Great Eastern, [ca. 1860] (Box 82)
  - Subjects--Ships--Naval ships, [ca. 1860-ca. 1920] (Box 82)
  - Subjects--Ships--Steamboats, [ca. 187--ca. 1910] (Box 82)
  - Subjects--Shops, [ca. 187--188-] (Box 82)
  - Subjects--Soda fountain, [ca. 1876] (Box 82)
  - Subjects--Spanish American War--Camp life, 1898 (Box 82)
  - Subjects--Spanish American War--Cuba, 1898-1899 (Box 82)
  - Subjects--Spanish American War--Dewey, 1898-1899 (Box 83)
  - Subjects--Spanish American War--Embarkments, 1898 (Box 83)
  - Subjects--Spanish American War--Marine, 1898-1899 (Box 83)
  - Subjects--Spanish American War--Marine, The Maine, 1898-1899 (Box 83)
  - Subjects--Spanish American War--Personalities, 1898-1902 (Box 84)
  - Subjects--Spanish American War--Philippines, 1898-1899 (Box 84)
  - Subjects--Spanish American War--Posed scenes, 1898-1899 (Box 84)
  - Subjects--Spanish American War--Rough Riders, 1898 (Box 84)
  - Subjects--Spanish American War--Groups, 1898-1899 (Box 84)
  - Subjects--Sports, games, recreation, [ca. 186--ca. 1910] (Box 84)
  - Subjects--Winter, [1860-ca. 188-] (Box 84)
  - Subjects--World War I, 1914-1918 (Box 85)
  - Comic & Sentimental--Children, [ca. 185--ca. 1910] (Box 85)
  - Comic & Sentimental--Dance, 1897-1905 (Box 86)
  - Comic & Sentimental--Diables, [ca. 1868-ca. 1880] (Box 86)
  - Comic & Sentimental--Domestic activities, [ca. 186--1897] (Box 86)
  - Comic & Sentimental--Ethnic stereotypes, [ca. 1865-ca. 189-] (Box 86)
  - Comic & Sentimental--Evils of drink, 1870, 1892 (Box 86)
  - Comic & Sentimental--Holidays, [ca. 186--ca. 188-] (Box 86)
  - Comic & Sentimental--Male/Female Role reversal, 1876-1902 (Box 86)
  - Comic & Sentimental--Marriage, [ca. 187--1907] (Box 86)
  - Comic & Sentimental--Marital infidelity, [1899-ca. 1905] (Box 86)
  - Comic & Sentimental--Music and entertainments, [187-] (Box 86)
  - Comic & Sentimental--Occupations, [ca. 1865- 1904] (Box 86)
  - Comic & Sentimental--Outdoor activities, [ca. 187--1900] (Box 87)
  - Comic & Sentimental--Risque, [ca. 189--ca. 1900] (Box 87)
  - Comic & Sentimental--Romance, [ca. 186--ca. 190-] (Box 87)
  - Comic & Sentimental--Women, [ca. 186--ca. 190-] (Box 87)
  - Comic & Sentimental--European, Alphabets des costumes, [ca. 186-] (Box 87)
  - Comic & Sentimental--European, angels, dreams, ghosts, [ca. 185--186-] (Box 87)
  - Comic & Sentimental--European, Characters & scenes, [185--ca. 186-] (Box 87)
  - Comic & Sentimental--European, Children, [185--ca. 187-] (Box 87)
  - Comic & Sentimental--European, Crinolines, [185-] (Box 87)
  - Comic & Sentimental--European, Domestic scenes, [185--ca. 186-] (Box 87)
  - Comic & Sentimental--European, Entertainment, [185--ca. 186-] (Box 88)
  - Comic & Sentimental--European, Holidays, [185--ca. 186-] (Box 88)
  - Comic & Sentimental--European, Occupations, [185--ca. 187-] (Box 88)
  - Comic & Sentimental--European, Religion, [185--ca. 186-] (Box 88)
  - Comic & Sentimental--European, Risque, [185--ca. 187-] (Box 88)
  - Comic & Sentimental--European, Romance and marriage, [185--ca. 187-] (Box 88)
  - Comic & Sentimental--European, Still-lifes, [185-] (Box 88)
  - Comic & Sentimental--European, Women, [185--ca. 187-] (Box 88)